Panama-Pacific International Exposition
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Panama-Pacific International Exposition
2.1.1.1.25.1
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1240
- Panama-Pacific International Exposition, 2.1.1.1.25.1
  - Tower of Jewels, 1915; 12; 2; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Arch of the Rising Sun, 1915; 13; 3; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Niche in Court of Seasons, 1915; 14; 4; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Fountain of Evening[?] in Court of Universe, 1915; 15; 5; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Italian Tower in Court of Flowers, 1915; 16; 6; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Kneeling figure, Fine Arts Palace, 1915; 17; 7; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Muse finding the head of Orpheus, 1915; 18; 8; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Tower of Jewels, 1915; 19; 9; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Organ Tower, Court of Abundance, 1915; 20; 10; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Entrance to Machinery Palace, 1915; 21; 11; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Fountain of Energy, 1915; 22; 12; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Italian Tower, 1915; 23; 13; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Italian Tower and Tower of Jewels, 1915; 24; 14; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Tower of Jewels, 1915; 25; 15; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - California Building, 1915; 26; 16; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Promenade, California Building, 1915; 27; 17; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Court of Palms, 1915; 28; 18; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Doorway of Educational Palace, 1915; 29; 19; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Glimpse of rotunda, Fine Arts Building, 1915; 30; 20; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Fountain of Energy, 1915; 31; 21; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Atlantic Ocean, statue of mermaid and fish, 1915; 32; 22; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Aquatic nymphs, 1915; 33; 23; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Reflections of colonnades in Fine Arts Palace, 1915; 34; 24; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Fountain of El Dorado, 1915; 35; 25; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Winter in Court of Four Seasons, 1915; 36; 26; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Fountain, Fine Arts Palace, 1915; 37; 27; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Promenade, 1915; 38; 28; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Horticultural Palace, 1915; 39; 29; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Looking through colonnade in Court of Seasons, 1915; 40; 30; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Court of Abundance, 1915; 41; 31; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Fine Arts Palace from lagoon, 1915; 42; 32; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Palace of Horticulture from Tower of Jewels, 1915; 43; 33; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Fine Arts Palace, 1915; 44; 34; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Educational Palace, 1915; 45; 35; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Lagoon walk, Fine Arts Palace, 1915; 46; 36; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Birds eye view of exposition, 1915; 47; 37; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Colonnades, Fine Arts Palace, 1915; 48; 38; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Horticulture Palace from South Gardens, 1915; 49; 39; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Entrance to Court of Four Seasons showing Fountain of Ceres, 1915; 50; 40; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Glimpse of exposition from Presidio, 1915; 51; 41; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Detail of fountain, Court of Abundance, 1915; 52; 42; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Festival Hall, 1915; 53; 43; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - Fountain of Youth, 1915; 54; 44; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  Box 1241
- Panama-Pacific International Exposition, 2.1.1.1.25.1
  - Fountain in Court of Abundance, 1915; 1; 45; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Rotunda of Fine Arts Palace, 1915; 2; 46; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Wildflower, statue of child, 1915; 3; 47; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Glimpse through colonnades, Fine Arts Palace, 1915; 4; 48; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Arches of the Rising and Setting Sun, 1915; 5; 49; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - On the marina, Adventurous Bowman, 1915; 6; 56; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Statue of Autumn in Court of Four Seasons, 1915; 7; 69; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Winter, Court of Four Seasons, 1915; 8; 73; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Bull of Sacrifice, 1915; 9; 74; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Descending Night, 1915; 10; 80; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Fountain of El Dorado, 1915; 11; 83; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - The South Sea, detail, Fountain of Energy, 1915; 12; 87; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - End of the Trail, 1915; 13; 88; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - The Pacific Ocean, detail, Fountain of Energy, 1915; 14; 89; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - North Sea, detail, Fountain of Energy, 1915; 15; 91; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Nations of the West, 1915; 16; 94; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Fountain of Ceres, 1915; 17; 95; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - End of the Trail, 1915; 18; 112; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Portal, Education Palace, Avenue of Palms, 1915; 19; 114; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Rising Sun, 1915; 20; 116; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Fire, mural painting by Brangwyn, 1915; 21; 117; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Water, mural painting by Frank Brangwyn, 1915; 22; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Earth, mural painting by Frank Brangwyn, 1915; 23; 119; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Water, mural painting by Frank Brangwyn, 1915; 24; 120; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Earth, mural painting by Frank Brangwyn, 1915; 25; 121; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Fire, mural painting by Frank Brangwyn, 1915; 26; 122; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Air, mural painting by Frank Brangwyn, 1915; 27; 123; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Air, mural painting by Frank Brangwyn, 1915; 28; 124; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - The Scout, 1915; 29; 128; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Fountain, Fine Arts Building, 1915; 30; 129; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - The Duck Baby, 1915; 31; 132; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - The Star, 1915; 32; 133; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Fine Arts Palace illuminated, 1915; 33; 134; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Arch of the Setting Sun, Court of Universe, 1915; 34; 135; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Nations of the East, 1915; 35; 136; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Adventurous Bowman, 1915; 36; 137; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Organ Tower, 1915; 37; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Building, palms in foreground, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 38; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Palm trees, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 39; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Flowerbeds and trees, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 40; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Flowers and road, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 41; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Man sitting under large tree, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 42; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Flowering bushes, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 43; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Road, flowers and trees, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 44; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Flowers, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 45; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Rock formations, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 46; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Rock formation, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 47; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Large rock formations, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 48; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - Industry on the water, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 49; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - City, clock tower, at night, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 50; 5x7 (Box 1241)
  - House, many plants in foreground, San Francisco[?], circa 1915; 51; 5x7 (Box 1241)